{"quiz": {"questions": [{"Hint": null, "question": "What may Helmuth not have realized all?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "that it meant"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "that it meant"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 173, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Will many of you know something about the Nazis and Hitler?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 172, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Had his father been a Nazi and a supporter of Adolf Hitler?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 171, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What will many of you know?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "something about the Nazis and Hitler"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "something about the Nazis and Hitler"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 170, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who will many of you know something about?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "about the Nazis and Hitler"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "about the Nazis and Hitler"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 169, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "May Helmuth not have realized all that it meant?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 168, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who had his father been?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "a Nazi and a supporter of Adolf Hitler"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "a Nazi and a supporter of Adolf Hitler"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 167, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who had his father been a Nazi and a supporter of?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "of Adolf Hitler"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "of Adolf Hitler"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 166, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Will many of Helmuth know something about the Nazis and Hitler?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 165, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Had Helmuth's father been a Nazi and a supporter of Adolf Hitler?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": ""}], "type": "mcq", "id": 164, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What will know something about the Nazis and Hitler?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "many of you"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "many of you"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 163, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What may Helmuth not have realized that it meant?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "all"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "all"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 162, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who may not have realized all that it meant?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "Helmuth"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "Helmuth"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 161, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "What will many of Helmuth know?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "something about the Nazis and Hitler"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "something about the Nazis and Hitler"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 160, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who will know something about the Nazis and Hitler?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "many of Helmuth"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "many of Helmuth"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 159, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who will many of Helmuth know something about?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "about the Nazis and Hitler"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "about the Nazis and Hitler"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 158, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who had Helmuth's father been?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "a Nazi and a supporter of Adolf Hitler"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "a Nazi and a supporter of Adolf Hitler"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 157, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who had Helmuth's father been a Nazi and a supporter of?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "of Adolf Hitler"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "of Adolf Hitler"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 156, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Whose father had been a Nazi and a supporter of Adolf Hitler?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "Helmuth's father"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "Helmuth's father"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 155, "skippable": true}, {"Hint": null, "question": "Who had been a Nazi and a supporter of Adolf Hitler?", "options": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "Helmuth's father"}, {"Description": null, "id": 2, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 3, "option": ""}, {"Description": null, "id": 4, "option": ""}], "time": null, "answer": [{"Description": null, "id": 1, "option": "Helmuth's father"}], "type": "mcq", "id": 154, "skippable": true}]}}